<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2013, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 10:25:00 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 10:25:00 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>MacBook Air the Ultimate Laptop</title>
<link>http://www.theverge.com/2013/6/17/4436332/macbook-air-review-13-inch-2013</link>
<description>Technology writer Nilay Patel of The Verge takes a close look at Apple’s 13-inch MacBook Air, which he calls “the best overall laptop on the market.” He notes that “the backlit keyboard is solid-feeling and comfortable, and Apple’s multitouch glass trackpad remains leaps and bounds ahead of the Windows competition.” But it’s the long-lasting battery that he appreciates most. Patel describes getting over 12 hours of battery life during his tests, “the record for a laptop running our test without an external battery.” Patel concludes, “The new Air is the first of a dramatic new breed of computer — it lets you set up a mobile office for a full day without concern for power.”</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 11:45:01 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Third Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/07/23Apple-Reports-Third-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced financial results for its fiscal 2013 third quarter ended June 29, 2013. The Company posted quarterly revenue of $35.3 billion and quarterly net profit of $6.9 billion, or $7.47 per diluted share. Apple sold 31.2 million iPhones, which set a June quarter record. Apple also sold 14.6 million iPads and 3.8 million Macs during the quarter. “We are especially proud of our record June quarter iPhone sales of over 31 million and the strong growth in revenue from iTunes, Software and Services,” said Apple CEO Tim Cook. “We are really excited about the upcoming releases of iOS 7 and OS X Mavericks, and we are laser-focused and working hard on some amazing new products that we will introduce in the fall and across 2014.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 14:40:55 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Unveils Logic Pro X</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/logic-pro/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has released Logic Pro X, the most advanced version of its professional recording studio for the Mac. Featuring a modern new design, Logic Pro X comes with new plug-ins, sounds, and tools that keep the music-making process flowing. New features include Drummer, a virtual session player that jams along with your songs, and Flex Pitch, which allows you to fine-tune the pitch of your audio tracks. Also new is Logic Remote, an app that lets you control Logic Pro X wirelessly from your iPad. “Logic Pro X is our most powerful version yet, with advanced tools and a modern new interface designed to streamline the process of creating professional quality music,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. Wayne Sermon, guitarist of the Platinum-selling band Imagine Dragons, said, “We love the new design, and the creative features of Logic Pro X have already been inspiring us to write new material while we’re on tour.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 10:57:14 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>App Store Marks 5 Years of App-ortunity</title>
<link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/columnist/talkingtech/2013/07/09/5-years-of-apple-apps/2499299/</link>
<description>USA Today tech columnist Jefferson Graham marks the fifth anniversary of Apple’s App Store by tracing its history and highlighting some of its successes. He notes that the App Store — which started out with 500 apps and now has over 900,000 — led the mobile boom and ushered in the end of the PC era. Graham interviews Instagram co-founder Kevin Systrom, who remembers his app’s launch in 2010: “I figured if we were lucky, we’d have 2,500 sign-ups on our first day. Instead, we got 25,000.” Since then, over 16 billion photos have been shared on Instagram. Graham also speaks to executives from Pandora and eBay about the impact the App Store has made on their companies. </description>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 11:35:34 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ducati Hits the Road Full Throttle with iPad</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/business/profiles/ducati/#video-ducati?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>A new video shows how Italian motorcycle maker Ducati uses iPad to integrate all business-related communication throughout the company, whose distribution and sales operation spans 88 countries. Ducati created a custom app that helps dealers place orders, track inventory, configure customers’ dream bikes, check a motorcycle’s history, train employees, and more. “iPad is a real revolution in the way we communicate with both our dealer network and our customers,” says Cristiano Silei, Ducati’s Vice President of Global Sales. “It’s fast, cool technology.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 14:20:45 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HBO GO, WatchESPN, and More Come to Apple TV  </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/06/19HBO-GO-WatchESPN-Come-to-Apple-TV.html ?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that HBO GO and WatchESPN are now available directly on Apple TV. HBO subscribers get unlimited access to their favorite HBO shows, and WatchESPN delivers a one-stop video destination for sports fans. In addition, three other new content providers are available today: Sky News, Crunchyroll, and Qello, offering live news and current TV programming. “We continue to offer Apple TV users great new programming options, combined with access to all of the incredible content they can purchase from the iTunes Store,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. iTunes users have downloaded more than one billion TV episodes and 380 million movies from iTunes to date, and they are purchasing over 800,000 TV episodes and over 350,000 movies per day.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 13:14:48 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Awarded $30 Million iPad Deal From L.A. Unified School District </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/06/19Apple-Awarded-30-Million-iPad-Deal-From-LA-Unified-School-District.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has won a $30 million contract from the Los Angeles Unified School District to begin providing an iPad to every student at the nation’s second-largest public school district. “The Board voted unanimously for Apple because iPad rated the best in quality, was the least expensive option, and received the highest scoring by the review panel that included students and teachers,” said Deputy Superintendent Jaime Aquino. Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing, Philip Schiller, said: “Education is in Apple’s DNA and we’re thrilled to work with Los Angeles Unified public schools on this major initiative as they plan to roll out iPads to every student across 47 campuses this fall.”
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 13:10:27 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Brings All-Day Battery Life to MacBook Air </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/macbook-air/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated MacBook Air with all-day battery life, fourth-generation Intel Core processors with faster graphics, 802.11ac Wi-Fi, and flash storage that is up to 45 percent faster than the previous generation. The 11-inch models feature double the storage of the previous model, and 13-inch models now start at a new lower price of $1,099. “MacBook Air is the industry leader for thin and light notebooks, and now with longer battery life, we’ve set the bar even higher,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “With faster flash, more powerful graphics and up to 12 hours of battery life, the new MacBook Air packs even more performance into the portable and durable design our customers love.” Apple also introduced completely redesigned AirPort Extreme and AirPort Time Capsule base stations featuring 802.11ac Wi-Fi for up to three times faster performance than the previous generation.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 13:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Releases Developer Preview of OS X Mavericks With More Than 200 New Features </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/osx/preview/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has released a developer preview of OS X Mavericks, the 10th major release of the Mac operating system. With more than 200 new features, OS X Mavericks brings Maps and iBooks to the Mac, introduces Finder Tags and Tabs, enhances multi-display support for power users, delivers new core technologies for breakthrough power efficiency and performance, and includes an all-new version of Safari. The preview release of OS X Mavericks is available to Mac Developer Program members starting Monday, and Mac users will be able to download Mavericks from the Mac App Store this fall.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 13:22:14 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces iTunes Radio </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/itunes/itunes-radio/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Announced today by Apple, iTunes Radio is a free Internet radio service featuring over 200 stations and an incredible catalog of music from the iTunes Store. When you tune into iTunes Radio on your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, Mac, PC, or Apple TV, you’ll have access to stations inspired by the music you already listen to, Featured Stations curated by Apple, and genre-focused stations that are personalized just for you. “It’s the music you love most and the music you’re going to love,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. Coming this fall, iTunes Radio is ad-supported and free for everyone, and iTunes Match users get iTunes Radio ad-free.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 13:21:31 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Gives Sneak Peek Into the Future of the Pro Desktop </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/mac-pro ?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today showed a sneak peek into the future of the pro desktop with a first look at the next-generation Mac Pro. It introduces a completely new pro desktop architecture and design that is optimized for performance inside and out. “With the latest Xeon processors, dual FirePro GPUs, ECC memory, PCIe-based flash and Thunderbolt 2, all built around a revolutionary thermal core, the next generation Mac Pro is the most radical Mac yet,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “All this performance and expandability is packed into a dramatic new design that’s one-eighth the volume, and best of all, it will be assembled here in the USA.” The next generation Mac Pro will be available later this year. </description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 13:02:59 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Unveils iOS 7 With Stunning User Interface &amp; Great New Features </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ios/ios7/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled iOS 7, the most significant iOS update since the original iPhone. iOS 7 is completely redesigned with subtle motion, an elegant color palette, and distinct, functional layers that make it feel more alive. The typography has been refined for a cleaner, simpler look, and the use of translucency and motion makes even simple tasks more engaging. iOS 7 has hundreds of great new features, including Control Center, Notification Center, improved Multitasking, AirDrop, Safari, Siri, and much more. “With what we’ve been able to achieve together, we see iOS 7 as an exciting new beginning,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering. The iOS 7 beta software and SDK are available immediately for iOS Developer Program members at developer.apple.com. iOS 7 will be available as a free software update for iPhone 4 and later, iPad 2 and later, iPad mini, and iPod touch (fifth generation) this fall.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 12:30:21 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bechtel Uses iPad and iOS to Build on Innovations </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/business/profiles/bechtel/#video-bechtel?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Bechtel, a global engineering company based in San Francisco, is featured in a new video that highlights how it uses iPad in the field. In addition to built-in apps, Bechtel has created its own apps. One focuses on worker safety at work sites, and another allows engineers create, update, and share technical information from their device. “iPad removes what in the past has been a huge barrier for construction projects,” says Eli Walter, Bechtel’s engineering manager. “It allows innovation to get out of the office and into the field where it belongs.”</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 13:11:20 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Justin Timberlake, Thirty Seconds to Mars, More Fan Favorites to Headline iTunes Festival in London </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/05/30Justin-Timberlake-Thirty-Seconds-to-Mars-Jack-Johnson-Jessie-J-Many-More-Fan-Favorites-to-Headline-iTunes-Festival-in-London.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that global superstars including Justin Timberlake, Thirty Seconds to Mars, Jack Johnson, and Jessie J are among the headliners at this year’s iTunes Festival in London. Running every night in September at the Roundhouse, the iTunes Festival features over 60 acts. Performances can be watched live or on-demand by millions of iOS users around the world on their iPhone, iPad, or iPod touch, as well as by music fans with iTunes on their computer or in HD with Apple TV. “This year’s iTunes Festival is the best ever with an incredible lineup of global superstars and stellar emerging artists,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. Fans can win tickets to the iTunes Festival through competitions run by local media partners.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 11:00:13 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mayo Clinic Brings New Innovations to Patient Care with iOS Apps </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad/business/profiles/mayo-clinic/ ?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>A new video features Mayo Clinic, which is using iPhone and iPad to transform how they care for patients. Practitioners say it’s helping patients and saving time. The clinic, known worldwide for its healthcare innovations, has developed a host of custom in-house apps, including one to give physicians instant access to patient records on an iOS device. Another app lets patients securely access their records and exchange messages with their providers. “For patients dealing with any health issue, information is power,” says Mayo’s Dr. Brad Leibovich. “The more we can empower them to understand what’s going on with them, the better they’ll feel and the better their outcomes will be.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 14:36:02 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple’s App Store Marks Historic 50 Billionth Download </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/05/16Apples-App-Store-Marks-Historic-50-Billionth-Download.html ?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that customers have now downloaded over 50 billion apps from the App Store. The 50 billionth app — Say the Same Thing by Space Inch, LLC — was downloaded by Brandon Ashmore from Mentor, Ohio, who received a $10,000 App Store Gift Card to commemorate the milestone. “The App Store completely transformed how people use their mobile devices and created a thriving app ecosystem that has paid out over nine billion dollars to developers,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “We’re absolutely floored to cross this milestone in less than five years.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2013 11:31:43 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ailing UK School Makes Dramatic Turnaround</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/education/profiles/essa/#video-essa?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>A new video profiles Essa Academy, a once struggling school in one of the most disadvantaged areas of England. New principal Showkat Badat has reinvented the school as a hub of technology-assisted learning, and helped incorporate an ecosystem of Apple products, including iPad, Mac, and iTunes U, into the classrooms. The students’ excitement about the technology and direct access to information is reflected in dramatically improved test scores. Since adopting the technology, Essa went from a 28 percent pass rate to 100 percent. “I don’t see technology as an add-on, a nice option to have,” says Badat. “It’s what enables learning and creates an environment that sparks creativity.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 15:57:38 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Is Tops When It Comes to Computer Tech Support </title>
<link>http://news.consumerreports.org/electronics/2013/04/apple-is-tops-when-it-comes-to-computer-tech-support.html</link>
<description>According to the latest Consumer Reports reader survey, Apple tops the list of brand-name computer manufacturers for the quality of its tech support, far surpassing other large companies. The report points to “ease of contacting staff, clarity of advice, technical knowledge, patience, and time for follow-up” in the phone and online support areas. Service at the Genius Bar rates equally highly. In addition, Apple improved on its own scores from last year’s survey.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 10:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Worldwide Developers Conference to Kick Off June 10 in San Francisco </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/04/24Apple-Worldwide-Developers-Conference-to-Kick-Off-June-10-in-San-Francisco.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple announced that it will hold its annual 
Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) June 10 through June 14 at San Francisco’s Moscone West. At the five-day conference, developers from around the world will learn about the future of iOS and OS X. WWDC will also feature more than 100 technical sessions presented by over 1,000 Apple engineers and hands-on labs to help developers integrate new technologies. And the popular Apple Design Awards will showcase the most outstanding apps available through the App Store and Mac App Store. Tickets for this year’s WWDC go on sale Thursday, April 25, at 10 a.m. PDT.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:41:32 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Second Quarter Results </title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2013/04/23Apple-Reports-Second-Quarter-Results.html</link>
<description>Apple announced financial results for its fiscal 2013 second quarter ended March 30, 2013, posting revenue of $43.6 billion and quarterly net profit of $9.5 billion, or $10.09 per diluted share. During the quarter, Apple sold 37.4 million iPhones, compared to 35.1 million in the year-ago quarter. And it sold 19.5 million iPads during the quarter, compared to 11.8 million in 2012. “We are pleased to report record March quarter revenue thanks to continued strong performance of iPhone and iPad,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “Our teams are hard at work on some amazing new hardware, software, and services, and we are very excited about the products in our pipeline.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 14:43:49 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>